[
  {
    "question": "1+1=",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "円周率の小数第25位は？",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "あ",
    "answers": [
      "い",
      "う",
      "え",
      "お"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "1+2=",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "1+3=",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "1+4=",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "1+5=",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "6",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "1+6=",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "7",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "1+7=",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "8",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "1+8=",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "9",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "1+9=",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "10",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }
]
